

✓ joahn@gmail.com✓ 1234567890⋄ pittusburg♦ www.qwikresume.com

# **Professional Summary**

PHR certified human resources professional with 7 years of experience who is well-versed in designing and administering recruiting, on-boarding, and compensation plans. I am looking to continue developing as a well-rounded HR manager at an established company like Purcell International Group.

## **Work Experience**

### HR manager

ABC Corporation Jan / 2022 - Ongoing new york

Human Resources Manager

StoreBound

March 2018 - current / New York, NY

Led new talent acquisition and recruitment processes for over

50 new full-time hires

Administered company-wide compensation and benefit plans

Conducted employee onboarding and helped organize over 1K

hours of training and development initiatives

Worked with team members 1 to 1 and in small groups to

enhance performance and employee satisfaction

### Hr coordinator

Company Title From - To Location

#### Uline

September 2014 - December 2015 / New York, NY

Scheduled interviews for candidates across 30 roles

Managed and administered 100% of pre-employment

assessments to prospective candidates

Assisted with new employee onboarding, and ensured all pre employment forms were completed within 72

hours

Collected feedback after final round interviews, and put together

comprehensive compensation packages for prospective hire

### **Education**

### **Human Resource Management University of Pittsburgh**

University of pittsburgh Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Location

# Skills

phr certification SAP2000 StruCalc

# **Achievements**

Award